<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nnamso Anthony</title>
    <description>I connect the Dot 
</description>
    <link>http://nnamso.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://nnamso.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 13:38:36 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 13:38:36 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>THE END OF APP STORES</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;Uber isn’t just killing the taxi industry. Its relentless approach to distribution and scale is also putting a nail in the coffin of app stores.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

Smart companies like Uber are rewriting the app distribution rulebook. Instead of being a bland icon lost amongst millions of others, they’ve chosen to aggressively accelerate their growth through deep integrations with services that people habitually use. It’s the start of a mass migration from the app store which is set to kill a long broken model for good.

&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 10:46:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/tech/2016/01/27/The-End-Of-App-Stores.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/tech/2016/01/27/The-End-Of-App-Stores.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jekyll Test Automation</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;Testing jekyll&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

When you treat content as code, you get the opportunity to co-opt best-of-breed developer workflows, and continuous integration is no exception. We’ve all been there. You make a simple change and end up breaking two or three other things. Links get out of date. Images move. Imagine if every time you made a change, all those things that you consciously or subconsciously worry about were automatically checked. Are my links accurate? Did any of my images break? Does this darn thing actually render the way I want it to? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

With CI services like Travis CI, whether public or private, adding continuous integration to a repository of prose content, whether an entire website or a collection of HTML or Markdown files becomes trivial, especially when you use open source tools like HTML Proofer.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Continuous integration (CI) is the idea that for every change, whether proposed or realized, a standard battery of tests run, to confirm the change does what you intend it to do. In most developer tools, like GitHub, you get instant feedback, in the form of a green light, to let you know that that is in fact the case, or a red light, in the event that something went awry, detailing exactly what doesn’t match you specified expectations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

With CI services like [Travis CI](https://travis-ci.org/), whether public or private, adding continuous integration to a repository of prose content, whether an entire website or a collection of HTML or Markdown files becomes trivial, especially when you use open source tools like [HTML Proofer](https://github.com/gjtorikian/html-proofer). &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 12:23:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/19/Jekyll-Test-Automation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/19/Jekyll-Test-Automation.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>general</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>URLs are how we share information today</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of years ago, the way humans shared information was through storytelling. Writing and the printing press shifted things towards written communication (passing around dead trees to share information), and the internet shifted us once again to the digital. Today, the primary means of sharing information with another human is through a URL. Maybe in 10 years we’ll have virtual 3D worlds and you’ll describe directions to walk to a virtual location to get information, but for now, URLs are the primary means by which an idea can be widely shared, and it does so by assigning a globally unique identifier to each. Want to share a Premium Times article? Send them a URL. A product on Konga? A funny Tweet? Whether you realize it or not, every major online system we use today creates unique URLs for each distinct idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself this: Has your organization’s workflow changed much since the Cold War? Since the advent of the internet? If you swapped out your laptop for a typewriter and email for inter-office couriers would the way you work be all that fundamentally different? From video conferencing to a distributed workforce to real-time chat, the tools available to organizations has radically shifted. Shouldn’t our workflows improve as a result of that shift, at least a little?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 12:23:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/18/urls.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/18/urls.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>general</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A message to my future self</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A message to your future self&lt;/strong&gt; – Ever go back and look at old code, only to scratch your head as to what&amp;#39;s going on? The same you that may be asking yourself what you were thinking when you got a tattoo five years back, is also going to be asking why you wrote that singleton function five years ago. Yet when you write open source, you mitigate that risk by explaining your code in such a way that others (including your future self) can understand it. In a world of system orientated architectures and ever-changing requirements, the chance that a software project is one-and-done is increasingly rare, not to mention the fact that by failing to properly document, you&amp;#39;re introducing a significant risk of vendor lock in. Your successor will thank you, and so will the person paying the bills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality of today&amp;#39;s business environment is that all software is inherently &amp;quot;open source&amp;quot;, even if the scope of the sharing is limited to an organization. Assume the software is open, needs to be modular, and will be repurposed, and you will save significant costs in the long run. And when you require the same of outside contractors, you get better, more flexible code, and offset the risks of vendor or technology lock in in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 12:23:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/18/A-message-to-your-future-self.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/18/A-message-to-your-future-self.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>general</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Am Sick And Tired</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/article_images/am-sick-and-tired/asat.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sick of people buying things they don’t want just to impress the people they don’t like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I’m tired of the media pushing these ugly African models&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trying to convince me they exotic when they just plain ugly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s not only one type of black beauty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sick of people sitting down complaining that there is no job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m tired of girls thinking that being attractive is an occupation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sick of Ghanaians still hating on Nigerians when we are suppose to be united.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sick of ladies having fake ass, fake breast, fake looks, and fake accent just to impress me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I want to smack people who don’t even realize Nigeria is a country and Africa is a continent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sick and tired of power outbreak in Nigeria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sick of police saying that bail is free, when I just paid 50,000 Naira in exchanged for his release and I was given no receipt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I’m sick of people bragging about the ghetto
the ghetto’s a situation we supposed to be getting out of not embracing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I’m sick of everybody trying to be in the entertainment industry
because soon, there’ll be no audience just a bunch of monkeys on stage dancing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still sick; I think I need panadol, what are your sick of?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 08:38:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/18/Am-Sick-And-Tired.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/18/Am-Sick-And-Tired.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>general</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phishing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/jc/p/3/005/0ae/202/21dc89e.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phishing is the attempt to acquire sensitive information such as usernames, passwords, and credit card details (and sometimes, indirectly, money) by masquerading as a trustworthy entity in an electronic communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phishing is a continual threat that keeps growing to this day. The risk grows even larger as Internet audience keeps increasing and it shows no sign of slowing down. You don’t have to be a hacker or get a 419-degree from Harvard only if that exist. It will take less than 10 minute to clone the UI (user interface) of any site online depending on the site size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how does this work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let say you own Amazon.com and I want to get peoples credit card number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simple&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will just have to buy Ammazon.com or Amazon.org clone the UI (user interface) upload it a server and that’s it. A user who doesn’t pay attention to URL then you have been served.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I get the card details into my database I will just redirect you to the original site and it’s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, my reason for writing this article is that a company hired me to do a background check on a company they wanted to buy from in Thailand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long story short&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After backtracking this company that literally doesn’t actually exist, I found out that they had two fake websites&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This first URL Claim to be the real site and referred to the second site as fake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pitoon Kan: In his words; they are fraud and they are hackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These made me recall the saying: A pot calling a kettle black&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) http://kanokpitonepaperindustrial.com/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) http://kanokpitonepaperindustry.com/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile the truth is that they are both fake site&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their plan was to make my client believe that the first site is genuine and the second one was not the genuine site. That will make him transfer the fund to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I requested to talk to them on Skype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a short conversation with the two parties they refuse to show up their faces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They said they use desktop system in their offices so they can’t do video call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s just a trick to say f*ck you I cant show you my face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please don’t transfer money to anyone account except you are using payment gateway like PayPal, visa, MasterCard etc. I say that because the bank at list has their details, I mean the account holder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be deceived&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to do background check first. Don’t let your emotions guide you and don’t be greedy. 95% percent of Internet fraud was accomplished because the defaulter was also a greedy person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t claim any money from Nigerian prince lol its not yours. Thanks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s how my client would have lost $1400. It might be small who know what would have happened next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I publish this article I will send them the link.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 08:13:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/security/2016/01/18/Phishing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/security/2016/01/18/Phishing.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>security</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building An Empire</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I LOVE THE WORD: Connecting the Dot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been connecting the dot for a while now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am building an empire. In the interest of helping people who might otherwise be inclined to believe that Stuff Just Happens, I thought I’d share my plan with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, before I am rich and famous, so when people accuse me of being disingenuous when I say I make my own luck, I can say “hey&amp;quot; didn’t you read my blog?”My plan is a twist on this simple and well-known classic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch Youtube.
???
Profit!
Maybe play video games…
OK, My real goal is to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[1] Make kickass software and change the world for the better. And make the world a better place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[2] Inspire &amp;amp; help a thousand designers/developers to launch their own products&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[3] Make alot of money&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[4] Yes, I want to be rich, famous, and influential. is that all? Well, I think so. Wouldn’t want to be greedy, now!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plan or do not plan, there is no luck&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you take yourself seriously, you have to plan. If you don’t take yourself seriously, you don’t have to plan — and, as we all know, a failure to plan, is a plan to fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Planning is a love letter to your future. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take myself seriously. And I loooooove my future and want it to feel that special love through time! So I plan.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 11:27:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/16/Building-An-Empire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/16/Building-An-Empire.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>general</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cognitive Virality</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://nnamso.github.io/assets/article_images/cognitive-virality/cognitive-virality.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;This research is as a result of my personal interest on why things go viral.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Virality of content circulated rapidly and widely from one Internet user to another: a viral ad campaign | the video went viral and was seen by millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Virality the tendency of an image, video, or piece of information to be circulated rapidly and widely from one Internet user to another; the quality or fact of being viral: new metrics will allow marketers to better assess the virality of their campaigns. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
More info will be disclosed soon. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 10:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/16/Cognitive-virality.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/general/2016/01/16/Cognitive-virality.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>general</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Billion Naira Mistake</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So today I have made up my mind to start a new blog. I have no idea where to start, or what I will be writing about. I am clueless at the moment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few years from now, I want to tell people that when I started this blog, I had no idea what I was going to write about. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is My Billion Naira Mistake ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would have started this blog a long time ago. But it is not too late to start right ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my new blog&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://nnamso.github.io/assets/images/nnamso1.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nnamso.github.io/new/year/2016/01/01/My-Billion-Naira-Mistake.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nnamso.github.io/new/year/2016/01/01/My-Billion-Naira-Mistake.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>new</category>
        
        <category>year</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
